Guide to the Frederic Bancroft Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Cataloged Correspondence
  - Kramer, Stella (Box 49)
  - Krans, Horatio S. (Box 49)
  - Kruttschnitt, Ernest R. (Box 49)
  - Krupp, Josephine (Box 49)
  - Lacey, Maude E. (Box 50)
  - Laing, G.J. (Box 50)
  - Lamb, Frederic G. (Box 50)
  - Lamb, James H. (Box 50)
  - Lamont, Hammond (Box 50)
  - Landou, H.A. (Box 50)
  - Lane, William C. (Box 50)
  - Langley, T.F. (Box 50)
  - LaPorte, T.A. (Box 50)
  - Lasner, Adelaide D.F. (Box 50)
  - Latane John H. (Box 50)
  - Latane, Elinor J.J. (Box 50)
  - Latimer, James B. (Box 50)
  - Laughlin, J. Lawrence (Box 50)
  - Lawley, Francis (Box 50)
  - Lawrence, George A. (Box 50)
  - Lawton & Cunningham (Box 50)
  - Lay, Henrietta Campbell (Box 50)
  - Leach Henry Goddard (Box 50)
  - Learned, H. Barrett (Box 50)
  - Lee, G.W.C. (Box 50)
  - Lee, S.H. (Box 50)
  - Lefavour, Henry (Box 50)
  - LeGrae, Anatole (Box 50)
  - Lehmann, J.W. (Box 50)
  - Lekus, Max (Box 50)
  - Leland, W.C. (Box 50)
  - Letour, Cora F. (Box 50)
  - Leutze, Eugene Henry Cozzens (Box 50)
  - Lewis, C.W. (Box 50)
  - L'Huillier, Theodore (Box 50)
  - Lincoln, Robert T. (Box 50)
  - lis, Francis B. (Box 50)
  - Livermore, W.R. (Box 50)
  - Lockwood, W.E. Jr. (Box 50)
  - Lodge, Henry C. (Box 50)
  - Logan, Warren (Box 50)
  - Lomax, L.L. (Box 50)
  - Lombard, E. (Box 50)
  - Longfellow, Alice M. (Box 50)
  - Longmans, Green & Co. (Box 50)
  - Longstreet, James (Box 50)
  - Longstreet, Mrs (Box 50)
  - Longworth, Nicholas (Box 50)
  - Loomis, Francis B. (Box 50)
  - Lorenzen, William C. (Box 50)
  - Loris-Malikoff (Box 50)
  - Lothrop, Thornton K. (Box 50)
  - Low, Seth (Box 50)
  - Lowden, Frank O. (Box 50)
  - Lowell, A Lawrence (Box 50)
  - Lowell, A.I. (Box 50)
  - Lowry, Adelaide D.P. (Box 50)
  - Lowry, Edward G. (Box 50)
  - Lowry, Elizabeth Lahey (Box 50)
  - Lowry, W. (Box 50)
  - Lucas, A. (Box 50)
  - Lucas, E.M. (Box 50)
  - Lyamberg, H.M. (Box 50)
  - McAdoo, William G. (Box 51)
  - McAneny, George (Box 51)
  - McCabe, W. Gordon (Box 51)
  - MacDonald, William (Box 51)
  - Mack, Max J. (Box 51)
  - Macmillan Company (Box 51)
  - MacVeagh, Eames (Box 51)
  - MacVeagh, Wayne (Box 51)
  - Maddax, R.G. (Box 51)
  - Madden, Martia B. (Box 51)
  - Magoffin, Ralph Van Deman (Box 51)
  - Mann, Claude (Box 51)
  - Mann, Claude (Box 51)
  - Mann, E.C. (Box 51)
  - Mann, Minerva M. (Box 51)
  - Marks, Mary S. (Box 51)
  - Martin, Caroline Colton (Box 51)
  - Martin, Hugh W (Box 51)
  - Martin, Isabella D. (Box 51)
  - Marye, George S. (Box 51)
  - Marye, L.S. (Box 51)
  - Maryland Agricultural College (Box 51)
  - Mason, Dr. & Mrs. (Box 51)
  - Mason, Emily V. (Box 51)
  - Mather, Robert (Box 51)
  - Mathisen, Mrs. Philip L (Box 51)
  - Matson, S.B. (Box 51)
  - Matthews, Lettie (Box 51)
  - Mattingly, Winfred M. (Box 51)
  - Mayo, Amory Dwight (Box 51)
  - Mayo, Katherine (Box 51)
  - McCain, Harry (Box 51)
  - McCall um, Mary Sherman (Box 51)
  - McCall, Henry (Box 51)
  - McCall, Sanuel Walker (Box 51)
  - McCarthy, Justin (Box 51)
  - McCheroen, J.A. (Box 51)
  - McClelland, Thomas (Box 51)
  - McClure, S.S. (Box 51)
  - McComas, Mary E. (Box 51)
  - McCord, J.H. (Box 51)
  - McCormack, Thomas J. (Box 51)
  - McCormick, Alexander (Box 51)
  - McCormick, Cyrus H. (Box 51)
  - McCormick, Maud Warner (Box 51)
  - McCullock, Susan (Box 51)
  - McDaniel, Joseph Hetherington (Box 51)
  - McDonald, William (Box 51)
  - McDonough, Joseph (Box 51)
  - McDougle, Stella M. (Box 51)
  - McElroy, R.M. (Box 51)
  - McKinley, William B. (Box 51)
  - McLane, J.H. (Box 51)
  - McLaughlin, Andrew Cunningham (Box 51)
  - McLeish, John E. (Box 51)
  - McMahon, Edward (Box 51)
  - McMaster, John B. (Box 51)
  - McNeir, William (Box 51)
  - McPherson, Jessie Cuthbert (Box 51)
  - McPherson, William L. (Box 51)
  - Meany, Edmond S. (Box 52)
  - Medill, Joseph (Box 52)
  - Meek, Tom Jones (Box 52)
  - Melton, Samuel W. (Box 52)
  - Meriwether, Coyler (Box 52)
  - Merrell, Irving S. (Box 52)
  - Merrill, E. (Box 52)
  - Merriman, Christina (Box 52)
  - Merritt, Alfred K. (Box 52)
  - Merrtvago, Mary (Box 52)
  - Meserve, Frederick H. (Box 52)
  - Meservey, S.T. (Box 52)
  - Metcalf, A.D. (Box 52)
  - Metcalf, Elizabeth (Box 52)
  - Metcalf, S.J. (Box 52)
  - Mica, Anthony (Box 52)
  - Michael, William H. (Box 52)
  - Michel, Frederick J. (Box 52)
  - Milburn, W.H. (Box 52)
  - Miles, L(ouis) Wardlaw (Box 52)
  - Miller, Elizabeth Smith (Box 52)
  - Millet, Francis Davis (Box 52)
  - Milliken, B.H. (Box 52)
  - Mills, Charles S. (Box 52)
  - Mills, Edward S. (Box 52)
  - Miner, William Harvey (Box 52)
  - Minneapolis Tribune editor (Box 52)
  - Mitchell, Broadus (Box 52)
  - Miyaoka, Tsunejiro (Box 52)
  - Monroe, George H. (Box 52)
  - Monroe, James (Box 52)
  - Monroe, Marie Jussen (Box 52)
  - Montgomery, Frank A. (Box 52)
  - Moore, Frederick W. (Box 52)
  - Morehead, Joseph M. (Box 52)
  - Morgan, James T. (Box 52)
  - Morgan, Octavins Vaughn (Box 52)
  - Morison, Sanuel Eliot (Box 52)
  - Morrell, Justin T. (Box 52)
  - Morse, John T. (Box 52)
  - Morse, John T., Jr. (Box 52)
  - Morton, C.E. (Box 52)
  - Morton, Elizabeth H. (Box 52)
  - Mosby, John S. (Box 52)
  - Moses, Bernard (Box 52)
  - Mosseby, John T. (Box 52)
  - Moton, Robert R. (Box 52)
  - Moulton, Ferris (Box 52)
  - Moulton, Frank I. (Box 52)
  - Munford, Edward W. (Box 52)
  - Munnerlyn, B.A. (Box 52)
  - Munroe, David A. (Box 52)
  - Munsterberg, Hugo (Box 52)
  - Muzzey, David S. (Box 52)
  - Myers, Ida Gilbert (Box 52)
  - National Cyclopedia of American Biography (Box 53)
  - Neale, Hattie Parker (Box 53)
  - Neale, S.C. (Box 53)
  - Neely, A.J. (Box 53)
  - Neeser, Robert W. (Box 53)
  - Nelson, H.L. (Box 53)
  - Nestor, Agnes (Box 53)
  - Neville, Edwin L. (Box 53)
  - Nevins, Allan (Box 53)
  - Newland, S. (Box 53)
  - Newlands, Janet (Box 53)
  - Newlands, Frances C. (Box 53)
  - Nichols, J.W. (Box 53)
  - Nicolay, Helen (Box 53)
  - Nicolay, John G. (Box 53)
  - Nishimaki, C. (Box 53)
  - Noble, Frederic Perry (Box 53)
  - Noel, Percy (Box 53)
  - Nordhoff, Walter (Box 53)
  - North, S.M. (Box 53)
  - Northwestern Trust Company (Box 53)
  - Norton, Charles D. (Box 53)
  - Norton, Miss Sara (Box 53)
  - Noyes, Alexander Dana (Box 53)
  - Noyes, ostello & Co. (Box 53)
  - O'Brien, F.G. (Box 53)
  - O'Brien, John W. (Box 53)
  - O'Connell, Daniel (1775-1847) (Box 53)
  - Odgers, George Allen (Box 53)
  - Oehler, Ira C. (Box 53)
  - Ogden, Rollo (Box 53)
  - Olds, Frederick A. (Box 53)
  - Oliver, Guy Eugene (Box 53)
  - Osgood, H.L. (Box 53)
  - Osterberg, Anne (Box 53)
  - Ota, Tadayuki (Box 53)
  - Otis, William K. (Box 53)
  - Owen, Thomas M. (Box 53)
  - Page, Thomas Nelson (Box 54)
  - Page, Walter Hines (Box 54)
  - Paine, Clarence S. (Box 54)
  - Paine, H.G. (Box 54)
  - Palfrey, John Gorham (Box 54)
  - Palmer, John McAuley (Box 54)
  - Parbnan, Francis (Box 54)
  - Park, Mary Fisk (Box 54)
  - Parker, Gilbert (Box 54)
  - Parker, W.B. (Box 54)
  - Parrish, Frank (Box 54)
  - Parsons, James R., Jr. (Box 54)
  - Parton, James (Box 54)
  - Patek, Stanislas (Box 54)
  - Phyre, J.F. (Box 54)
  - Patten, John S. (Box 54)
  - Paxson, Frederic L. (Box 54)
  - Peabody, Frederick W. (Box 54)
  - Peabody, George H. (Box 54)
  - Pearl, H.M. (Box 54)
  - Pearson, Henry Greenleaf (Box 54)
  - Pease, Arthur Stanley (Box 54)
  - Peck, H.J. (Box 54)
  - Peirce, Harvey (Box 54)
  - Pendleton, Louis (Box 54)
  - Pennington, J. Wilson (Box 54)
  - Penny, J. Andrade (Box 54)
  - Perry, Bliss (Box 54)
  - Phelps, F.S. (Box 54)
  - Phelps, G.S. (Box 54)
  - Phillips, Barnet (Box 54)
  - Phillips, Bertha (Box 54)
  - Phillips, J.S. (Box 54)
  - Phillips, J.T. (Box 54)
  - Phillips, Ulrich B. (Box 54)
  - Pierce, Antoinette B. (Box 55-57)
  - Pierce, Catherine W. (Box 58)
  - Pierce, Edbridge B. (Box 58)
  - Pierce, Wilson H. (Box 59)
  - Pilkington, Robert R. (Box 59)
  - Pinckney, Thomas (Box 59)
  - Pine, John B. (Box 59)
  - Piurce, Wilson H. (Box 59)
  - Polignac, C. de (Box 59)
  - Pond, George F. (Box 59)
  - Poole, W.F. (Box 59)
  - Pope, Joseph Daniel (Box 59)
  - Port, P.S. (Box 59)
  - Porter, H.W. (Box 59)
  - Porzelt, Paul (Box 59)
  - Poteet, W.C. (Box 59)
  - Potts, Elizabeth (Box 59)
  - Powell, Mary G. (Box 59)
  - Praetorius, Edward L. (Box 59)
  - Pratt, Helen F. (Box 59)
  - Preson, Roger A. (Box 59)
  - Price, Henry W. (Box 59)
  - Prince, George W. (Box 59)
  - Pringle, Elizabeth S. Allston (Box 59)
  - Pringle, Major TT. Gordon (Box 59)
  - Probst, J.H. (Box 59)
  - Prothero, .G.W. (Box 59)
  - Pryor, Roger Atkinson (Box 59)
  - Pulver, Clara (Box 59)
  - Push, J.L. (Box 59)
  - Putnam, George H. (Box 59)
  - Putnam, Herbert (Box 59)
  - Putnam, Ruth (Box 59)
  - Quincy, Josiah (Box 59)
  - Raines, C.W. (Box 60)
  - Rainey, Ella M. (Box 60)
  - Rainey, Henry T. (Box 60)
  - Rammelkamp, C.H. (Box 60)
  - Ranck, James B. (Box 60)
  - Randall, J.G. (Box 60)
  - Randolph, Carmen F. (Box 60)
  - Randolph, Coleman (Box 60)
  - Randolph, L.V.F. (Box 60)
  - Ranger, Stanley (Box 60)
  - Rankin, Margreat (Box 60)
  - Rankin, Martha (Box 60)
  - Ransom, M.W. (Box 60)
  - Rathbone, Henry R. (Box 60)
  - Raymond, Henry W. (Box 60)
  - Redpath (Box 60)
  - Reed, J. Archiebald (Box 60)
  - Reed, John C. (Box 60)
  - Reeves, J.S. (Box 60)
  - Reeves, W.P. (Box 60)
  - Reid, Whitelaw (Box 60)
  - Renard, E.H. (Box 60)
  - Reynier, Gustave (Box 60)
  - Rhodes, James F. (Box 61)
  - Rice, Clinton (Box 61)
  - Richardson, E.C. (Box 61)
  - Richardson, Frank W. (Box 61)
  - Richardson, William A. (Box 61)
  - Richmond, Henry A. (Box 61)
  - Ridder, Herman (Box 61)
  - Rider, George C. (Box 61)
  - Rider, Ina G. (Box 61)
  - Rilery, Forrest C. (Box 61)
  - Riley, Franklin L. (Box 61)
  - Rines, George E. (Box 61)
  - Rives, George Lockhart (Box 61)
  - Robert, M.G. (Box 61)
  - Roberts, Hazel (Box 61)
  - Roberts, Lavina E. (Box 61)
  - Roberts, Lavinia Cole (Box 61)
  - Roberts, M.A. (Box 61)
  - Roberts, Martin A. (Box 61)
  - Roberts, Mrs. F.C. (Box 61)
  - Robertson, Beverly H. (Box 61)
  - Robins, Sally Nelson (Box 61)
  - Robinson, Albert G. (Box 61)
  - Robinson, James (Box 61)
  - Robinson, Marrgan P. (Box 61)
  - Rockhill, N.N. (Box 61)
  - Rolfe, Alfred G. (Box 61)
  - Rollins, C.B. (Box 61)
  - Romero, M. (Box 61)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore (Box 61)
  - Root, Winfred T. (Box 61)
  - Rosenbaum, Belle (Box 61)
  - Rosenwal£, Julius (Box 61)
  - Rossiter, N.S. (Box 61)
  - Roth, Stanley H. (Box 61)
  - Rouard, Henri (Box 61)
  - Round, George C. (Box 61)
  - Rowland, Dunbar (Box 61)
  - Rowland, Irene (Box 61)
  - Rowland, Mrs. Dunbar (Box 61)
  - Royal Typewriter Company (Box 61)
  - Rubles, George (Box 61)
  - Ruffin, Julian N. (Box 61)
  - Russell, Charles Edward (Box 61)
  - Rust, H.L. (Box 61)
  - Sage, B.I. (Box 62)
  - Saito, Hirosi (Box 62)
  - Sakabe, Shigeyoshi (Box 62)
  - Salley, A.S., Jr. (Box 62)
  - Sampson, Celia (Box 62)
  - Sass, G.H. (Box 62)
  - Savage, P.C. (Box 62)
  - Sawada, S. (Box 62)
  - Schaefer, P.W. (Box 62)
  - Schafer, Joseph (Box 62)
  - Schenck, Robert C. (Box 62)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry (Box 62)
  - Schouler, James (Box 62)
  - Schurman, J.G. (Box 62)
  - Schurz, Agathe (Box 63)
  - Schurz, Carl (Box 64)
  - Schurz, Marianne (Box 64)
  - Schurz, S. & A. (Box 64)
  - Scott, Armond H. (Box 64)
  - Scott, Bancroft, Martin & Stephens (Box 64)
  - Scott, Emmitt J. (Box 64)
  - Scott, John W. (Box 64)
  - Screws, W.W. (Box 64)
  - Seaville, William H. (Box 64)
  - Sedgwick, Ellery (Box 64)
  - Sedgwick, W.T. (Box 64)
  - Seelye, Julie H. (Box 64)
  - Selby, Julian A. (Box 64)
  - Seligman, Edwin R. (Box 64)
  - Seller, J.L. (Box 64)
  - Seston, Notte (Box 64)
  - Seudelback, F.J. (Box 64)
  - Severance, Frank H. (Box 64)
  - Seward, Frederick W. (Box 64)
  - Seward, Olive Risby (Box 64)
  - Seward, William H. (Box 64)
  - Sewell, W.J. (Box 64)
  - Shaw, Albert (Box 65)
  - Shaw, Edgar D. (Box 65)
  - Sheba, S. (Box 65)
  - Sheba, Togo (Box 65)
  - Sheba, Toshi'ko (Box 65)
  - Shedd, John G. (Box 65)
  - Sheldon, Mary E. (Box 65)
  - Shepard, Edward M. (Box 65)
  - Sherman, Caroline Alvord (Box 65)
  - Sherman, John (Box 65)
  - Sherman, Loren A. (Box 65)
  - Sherman, P.T. (Box 65)
  - Sherrill, William H. (Box 65)
  - Sherwood, H. Foble (Box 65)
  - Shryock, Richard H. (Box 65)
  - Shugio, H. (Box 65)
  - Sibley, Willis E. (Box 65)
  - Sickless, General (Box 65)
  - Simpson, Sidney P. (Box 65)
  - Sioussat, St. George L. (Box 65)
  - Skehan & Bernheim (Box 65)
  - Skehan, James B. (Box 65)
  - Slayden, James L. (Box 65)
  - Sloane, William M. (Box 65)
  - Smedes, Susan Dabney (Box 65)
  - Smith and Smith (Box 65)
  - Smith, Bertrand H. (Box 65)
  - Smith, Edward (Box 65)
  - Smith, Ethel (Box 65)
  - Smith, Godwin (Box 65)
  - Smith, Hoke (Box 65)
  - Smith, Justin H. (Box 65)
  - Smith, Monroe (Box 65)
  - Smith, Randoph (Box 65)
  - Smith, Roland Cotton (Box 65)
  - Smith, St. Clair (Box 65)
  - Smith, Thomas C. (Box 65)
  - Sniff en, M.K. (Box 65)
  - Snoden, Yates (Box 65)
  - Snow, Freeman (Box 65)
  - Solberg, Thorwald (Box 66)
  - Sontohoff, Herbert (Box 66)
  - Sothoron, J. Thomas (Box 66)
  - Sowers, Bessie Z.T. (Box 66)
  - Sowers, Eleanor Kerfoot (Box 66)
  - Spencer, William B. (Box 66)
  - Spofford, A.R. (Box 66)
  - Spofford, Florence P. (Box 66)
  - Sprunt, James (Box 66)
  - Squiggins, George W. (Box 66)
  - St. Roman, Marie Rosine de (Box 66)
  - Stahel, Julius (Box 66)
  - Stakely, Davis F. (Box 66)
  - Stallo, Hulda (Box 66)
  - Stanard, W.G. (Box 66)
  - Stanley, Mary Garfield (Box 66)
  - Stanton, Theodore (Box 66)
  - Staple, R.A. (Box 66)
  - Stearns, Frank P. (Box 66)
  - Stenert, F.A. (Box 66)
  - Stephens, H. Morse (Box 66)
  - Stephenson, Nathaniel Wright (Box 66)
  - Stephenson, Wendell Holmes (Box 66)
  - Stevens, Frank S. (Box 66)
  - Stevens, Monfeld (Box 66)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis (Box 66)
  - Stewart, Lucy S. (Box 66)
  - Stewart. Charles W. (Box 66)
  - Stilwell, C.S. (Box 66)
  - Stilwell, D.S. (Box 66)
  - Stone, Alfred H. (Box 66)
  - Stone, Cora F. (Box 66)
  - Stone, F.D. (Box 66)
  - Stone, William (Box 66)
  - Storey, Moorfield (Box 66)
  - Stout, G.F. (Box 66)
  - Straus, Oscar S. (Box 66)
  - Street, W.H. (Box 66)
  - Strong, W. (Box 66)
  - Strong, Warren B. (Box 66)
  - Stuart, John (Box 66)
  - Sumner, John Osborne (Box 66)
  - Sumner, W.G. (Box 66)
  - Super, of Reading Rom, Lib. of Congress (Box 66)
  - Swain, Florence E. (Box 66)
  - Swift, Eben (Box 66)
  - Swift, Lucius B. (Box 66)
  - Swisher, Charles C. (Box 66)
  - Sylvester, Richard (Box 66)
  - Syndor, Charles S. (Box 66)
  - Szold, Robert (Box 66)
  - Takagi, Yasaka (Box 67)
  - Takashi, Komatsu (Box 67)
  - Taketomi. T. (Box 67)
  - Tanimura, Issa (Box 67)
  - Tansill, Charles C. (Box 67)
  - Tarbell, Ida M. (Box 67)
  - Tauaka, I. (Box 67)
  - Taylor, Graham (Box 67)
  - Taylor, J.F. (Box 67)
  - Taylor, W.H. (Box 67)
  - Temple, D.F. (Box 67)
  - Tenney, Eleanor F. (Box 67)
  - Tenney, Horace Kent (Box 67)
  - Terry, B.S. (Box 67)
  - Terry, Sadie Bancroft (Box 67)
  - Thayer, W.H. (Box 67)
  - The McClure Company (Box 67)
  - The Pullman Company (Box 67)
  - Thomas, Jesse O. (Box 67)
  - Thomas, Milton Halsey (Box 67)
  - Thornton, Helen (Box 67)
  - Thorpe, Francis N. (Box 67)
  - Thunoda (Box 67)
  - Times, The (Box 67)
  - Tisdel, Edine Frances (Box 67)
  - Titherington, Richard Handefield (Box 67)
  - Todd, Arthur J. (Box 67)
  - Tollman, Edgar B. (Box 67)
  - Tomaszewski, J. (Box 67)
  - Tourgee, Albion W. (Box 67)
  - Tout, T.F. (Box 67)
  - Townsend, E.W. (Box 67)
  - Tracy, George S. (Box 67)
  - Tracy, Howard van S. (Box 67)
  - Trent, W.P. (Box 67)
  - Tresch, Edward A. (Box 67)
  - Trescpt, William Henry (Box 67)
  - Trevelyan, George M. (Box 67)
  - Trexler, H.A. (Box 67)
  - Trieb, M. (Box 67)
  - Triepel, Emma M.V. (Box 67)
  - Trumbull, Frank (Box 67)
  - Trumbull, Lyman (Box 67)
  - Tsunoda, Riusaka (Box 67)
  - Tteyer, S.H. (Box 67)
  - Tuckerman, Emily (Box 67)
  - Tulane, Victor (Box 67)
  - Turley, George A. (Box 67)
  - Turner, George K. (Box 67)
  - Turner, Raymond (Box 67)
  - Tyler, Lyn G. (Box 67)
  - Ufford, Walter S. (Box 68)
  - Uliura, F. (Box 68)
  - Usher, Ellis B. (Box 68)
  - Van Norden, Theodore Langdon (Box 68)
  - Vanderlip, Frank A., Jr. (Box 68)
  - VanDoren, Carl (Box 68)
  - Vedder, O.F. (Box 68)
  - Vernadsky, G. (Box 68)
  - Verst, G.G. (Box 68)
  - Veynaud, Henry (Box 68)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison (Box 68)
  - Vincent, J.M. (Box 68)
  - Von Hoist, Belle (Box 68)
  - Von Hoist, Herman Eduard (Box 68)
  - Von Hoist, Mary (Box 68)
  - Von Hoist, Mrs. E (Box 68)
  - Von Naparid, Alfred (Box 68)
  - Vorhees, D.W. (Box 68)
  - Waddell, A.M. (Box 69)
  - Walker, Albert H. (Box 69)
  - Walker, Francis (Box 69)
  - Walker, Williston (Box 69)
  - Wallace, D.D. (Box 69)
  - Wallace, G.Gale (Box 69)
  - Wallgren, A.W.L. (Box 69)
  - Walmsley, James Elliott (Box 69)
  - Walter, Miriam R. (Box 69)
  - Wanamaker, John (Box 69)
  - Ward, Alice F. (Box 69)
  - Warfield, Ethelbert D. (Box 69)
  - Warren, Charles (Box 69)
  - Warren, F.B. (Box 69)
  - Warren, Fiske (Box 69)
  - Warren, Whitney (Box 69)
  - Warren, Winslow (Box 69)
  - Washburn, William Ives (Box 69)
  - Washburne, Hempstead (Box 69)
  - Washington Railway & Electric Co. (Box 69)
  - Washington, Booker T. (Box 69)
  - Washington, Booker T., Jr (Box 69)
  - Watin, E. (Box 69)
  - Watson, C.W. (Box 69)
  - Watson, Lucy D. (Box 69)
  - Watterson, Henry (Box 69)
  - Weatherford, W.D. (Box 69)
  - Webb, Alexander S. (Box 69)
  - Webb, Lucy R. (Box 69)
  - Webb, M.F. (Box 69)
  - Webb, W. Seward (Box 69)
  - Weed, Ella (Box 69)
  - Wein, Jessie W. (Box 69)
  - Welles, Edgar T. (Box 69)
  - Welles, H. Parker (Box 69)
  - Wellford, Beverley M. (Box 69)
  - Welling, James C. (Box 69)
  - Wells, Edward L. (Box 69)
  - Wells, H.G. (Box 69)
  - Wells, Katherine Belden (Box 69)
  - Welsh, William (Box 69)
  - Went, Stanley (Box 69)
  - Werner (Box 69)
  - Werner, Hermine (Box 69)
  - Weshit, Ralph (Box 69)
  - Wesleyan College (Box 69)
  - West, E.P.H. (Box 69)
  - Wharton, Francis (Box 69)
  - Wharton, T.F. (Box 69)
  - Wheeler, Everett P. (Box 69)
  - Wheeler, Joseph (Box 69)
  - Wheeler, Robert (Box 69)
  - Whelpley, Edgar J. (Box 69)
  - White, A.R. (Box 70)
  - White, E.D. (Box 70)
  - White, George W. (Box 70)
  - White, Henry Alexander (Box 70)
  - White, Horace (Box 70)
  - White, Laura A. (Box 70)
  - White, Leila O. (Box 70)
  - White, Martha R. (Box 70)
  - White, Mrs. Helen S. (Box 70)
  - White, S.V. (Box 70)
  - Whitelaw, Jane M. (Box 70)
  - Whitman, Benaiah Longley (Box 70)
  - Whitridge, Frederic W. (Box 70)
  - Wickersham, George W. (Box 70)
  - Wickinson, W.C. (Box 70)
  - Wigmore, John H. (Box 70)
  - Wilby, Joseph (Box 70)
  - Wilcox, C.W. (Box 70)
  - Wilder, B.C. (Box 70)
  - Wilder, B.H. (Box 70)
  - Wiley, B.I. (Box 70)
  - Wilgus, Horace E. (Box 70)
  - Wilkinson, Alfred (Box 70)
  - Wilkinson, W.C. (Box 70)
  - Williamston, Howard (Box 70)
  - Willard, James F. (Box 70)
  - Willcox, William G. (Box 70)
  - Williams, Charles F. (Box 70)
  - Williams, Charles P. (Box 70)
  - Williams, David R. (Box 70)
  - Williams, E.P. (Box 70)
  - Williams, Frances (Box 70)
  - Williams, Gardner F. (Box 70)
  - Williams, George Frederick (Box 70)
  - Willis, H. Parker (Box 70)
  - Wilson, Bluford (Box 71)
  - Wilson, Flora (Box 71)
  - Wilson, Francis (Box 71)
  - Wilson, Gen. Jas Grant (Box 71)
  - Wilson, Jaraes H. (Box 71)
  - Wilson, N.H. (Box 71)
  - Wilson, Walter (Box 72)
  - Wilstach, Paul (Box 72)
  - Winkler, F.C. (Box 72)
  - Winn, E.J. (Box 72)
  - Winn, Elizabeth Jarvis (Box 72)
  - Winson, Justin (Box 72)
  - Winthrop, Robert Y. (Box 72)
  - Wise, Jennings C. (Box 72)
  - Wolf, Henry M. (Box 72)
  - Wood, R. Francis (Box 72)
  - Woodburn, James A. (Box 72)
  - Woodford, Stewart L. (Box 72)
  - Woodson, Carter G. (Box 72)
  - Woodward, Liby (Box 72)
  - Woodward, Robett Simpson (Box 72)
  - Wordsworth, William (Box 72)
  - Worthington, Valeria (Box 72)
  - Wortin, E. (Box 72)
  - Wright, J. Butler (Box 72)
  - Wright, Marcus J. (Box 72)
  - Wylly, Charles S. (Box 72)
  - Yates, Richard (Box 72)
  - Yoneda, Kiyotaka (Box 72)
  - Young, Cora Rugar (Box 72)
- Series II: Letterbooks and Bills
  - Letterbooks (Box 73)
  - Bills, receipts, etc. (Box 74)
- Series III: Manuscripts
  - Carl Schurz - notes (Box 1) (Box 75)
  - Carl Schurz - corrected manuscript (Box la) (Box 76)
  - Carl Schurz - page proof - v. 1,2 (Box 2) (Box 77)
  - Carl Schurz - page proof - v. 3,4 (Box 3) (Box 78)
  - Carl Schurz - page proof - v. 5,6 (Box 4) (Box 79)
  - Carl Schurz - plate proof - v. 1,2 (Box 5) (Box 80)
  - Carl Schurz - plate proof - v. 3,6 (Box 6) (Box 81)
  - Carl Schurz - plate proof - v. 4,5 (Box 7) (Box 82)
  - Southern History (Box 8) (Box 83)
  - Old South (Box 8a) (Box 84)
  - Old South (Box 8b) (Box 85)
  - Old South (Box 9) (Box 86)
  - Negro and Slavery - notes etc. (Box 10) (Box 87)
  - Negro and Slavery - notes etc. (Box 11) (Box 88)
  - Negro and Slavery - notes etc. (Box 12) (Box 89)
  - Journal of the Convention of the People of South Carolina (Box 90)
  - Edward Bates Diary - typescript; John G. Reed - August 5, 1908 (Box 13) (Box 90)
  - William H. Seward (Box 14) (Box 91)
  - Diaries of Southern Trips; Frederic Harrison; Gideon Welles (Box 92)
  - Miscellaneous articles; (Box 15) (Box 92)
  - Notes on the Civil War (Box 16) (Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 17) (Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous Notes; Edwin B. Hewes - lecture notes; (Box 18) (Box 95)
  - College Notes and College Essays (Box 19) (Box 96)
  - Lecture Notes; Page Proof for Correspondence of Toombs, Stephens and Cobb; (Box 20) (Box 97)
  - University of Chicago Lecture Notes, 1897 (Box 21) (Box 98)
  - Washington Notebooks (7 vols.); Essay about the Constitutional Convention of 1787-88; (Box 22) (Box 99)
  - Miscellaneous Transcripts and Notes (Box 23) (Box 100)
- Series IV: Scrapbooks
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1) (Box 101)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings (Box 2) (Box 102)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings (Box 3) (Box 103)
  - Confederate Clippings (Box 4) (Box 104)
  - Carl Schurz Scrapbook; Present Condition of Mexico (Box 5) (Box 105)
  - Scrapbook (volume 1) (Box 148)
- Series V: Clippings and Photographs
  - Clippings and Reprints (Box 106-109)
  - Photographs (Box 110)
- Series VI: Edgar Bancroft Files
  - Subseries VI.1: Clippings and Correspondence
    - A -B (Box 111)
    - C (Box 112)
    - D -H (Box 113)
    - I -L (Box 114)
    - M -N (Box 115)
    - P -Re (Box 116)
    - Ro --U (Box 117)
    - War - Wo (Box 118)
    - Southern History - original manuscript (Box 119)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 120-121)
  - Subseries VI.2: Diaries and Memorabilia
    - Diaries and Memorabilia (Box 122)
  - Subseries VI.3: Speech File
    - Index and Nos. 1 - 15 (Box 123)
    - Nos.. 16 -27 (Box 124)
    - Nos.. 28 -35 (Box 125)
    - Nos.. 36 -42 (Box 126)
    - Nos.. 43 -60 (Box 127)
    - Nos.. 61 -70 (Box 128)
    - Nos,. 71 -81 (Box 129)
    - Nos.. 82 -97 (Box 130)
    - Nos.. 98 -111 (Box 131)
    - Nos,. 112 - 123 (Box 132)
    - Nos,. 124 - 131 (Box 133)
    - Nos.. 132 - 143 (Box 134)
    - Nos.. 144 - 152 (Box 135)
  - Subseries VI.4: Additional Arranged Files
    - Letters of Condolence received by Frederic Bancroft upon the death of Edgar Bancroft (Box 136)
    - Miscellaneous Notebooks (Box 137-139)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 140)
    - Personal Materials (letters, photos, diaries, etc.) (Box 141)
    - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 142)
    - Correspondence with J.Rhodes (Box 143)
    - Schurz Manuscript (Box 144)
    - Copies of Seward Manuscript (Box 145)
    - Books (Box 146)
    - Book of Articles (Box 147)
    - Picture of Frederic Bancroft in his Studio